webknowhow.net 2018-03-12

# DevStart.com - The Web Developers Resource Center | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy. This policy covers how DevStart treats personal information that is received, including your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. We collect information from your browser, including your IP addresses and the page you request. We might ask for your contact information when you correspond with us, call us to request service, register to attend a seminar, or participate in an online survey.

Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement.

The site contains links to other sites at which personal information is collected. In such instances, unless expressly provided to the contrary, the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site.

DevStart does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested us.

DevStart uses data from Google's Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender and interests) with Google Analytics.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or otherwise required by law.

Note that we may update this policy without notifying you personally.
